He has a lot of fans.
You don't even know Jinxi?
I don't know.
Stop.
Bai Feixin.
You came in early. Why
did you keep singing?
And the music,
why did it keep playing?
Did no one notice the problem?
Director.
It's a problem that Feixin came in early.
But Heying,
why did you sing along?
Do you think it doesn't matter?
How many times have you two
rehearsed this song?
Are you tired of it?
No matter how many times
you've done it,
to the audience,
it's always the first time.
Understood?
Did you hear me?
Understood.
Bye, director.
Here we go again.
Starting what?
Today is
the last
performance of "Jianjia".
Then we'll start rehearsing Nie Xiaoqian.
"A Chinese Ghost Story".
Every time
we transition from old to new,
you get really irritable.
Do I?
Don't you?
Even your legs aren't as stiff
as your stubborn mouth.
They said you're not going to the dinner tonight.
Why not?
What will you do staying home alone?
"One Hundred Years of Solitude".
It's not like we're splitting up after this show.
We'll still be working together on the next one.
Today's performance was a great success.
That's exactly why we need to relax.
That's why we should celebrate, right?
Don't be so tense.
I don't like going to group dinners.
It's not with us.
Do you remember Kevin?
Kevin has a very good friend joining us today.
He's a top-tier executive.
Ning Jin.
What are you going home for?
Are you going to spend the rest of your life
with your cat?
That actually sounds pretty good.
It's better than finding an unreliable man.
That really won't do.
Why not?
How long has it been since you dated someone?
How long has it been
since you felt that flutter,
that heart-pounding sensation,
or butterflies in your stomach?
I just don't get butterflies in my stomach.
And I think I'm doing just fine like this.
I'm heading back.
Anyway, I saw someone online say
that the romance in "Jianjia"
is a bit bland.
Who said that?
Find it and let me see.
I don't know.
There are also follow-up comments agreeing with it.
Which comment?
Show it to me.
Does it matter?
Who always tells us during rehearsals
that art comes from life?
Rehearsals for 'A Chinese Ghost Story' are about to start.
Have you figured it out?
How to write the romance between
Nie Xiaoqian and Ning Caichen?
Why don't you awaken the butterflies
in your stomach?
If you wait any longer,
they'll get too old to flutter.
The feeling of a heartbeat.
Thump-thump.
The feeling of love.
I'm sorry.
I lied about keeping you company.
I won't be a third wheel.
I'm going to a dinner party.
Have fun!
I knew it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What do you think of this place?
It's pretty good.
Did you notice?
The one singing on stage is Mochou.
A friend of mine opened this place.
It's members-only.
Many celebrities like to come here.
You people in the art circles
should like it here.
I'm not in any art circle.
Directing is my profession.
It's not for playing around.
You're very assertive.
I like it.
I have quite a few director friends.
They told me
that people in your profession
have a strong desire to create.
Right?
I guess so.
Then I hope all your desires
can be satisfied.
This cocktail
isn't very strong.
Drink this.
This will make it much stronger.
Bottoms up.
No.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Miss Ning.
Director.
You are so beautiful.
I know I am beautiful.
But do you know
what a beautiful female director
after entering the industry
must learn first?
What is it?
Don't get yourself too drunk.
So you won't be
taken advantage of by
some greasy middle-aged investors.
No,
what do you mean?
With your alcohol tolerance,
even if you take me away today,
you can't do anything.
Why don't you go back
before you black out?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Stop pretending.
How is my heart
supposed to skip a beat?
What on earth am I doing?
Come to my office right away.
Jin Xi?
Yes.
Jin Xi.
Why are you
looking at me so confused?
You don't even know him?
Why do I need to know who he is?
You have to know who he is.
Jin Xi.
He's the music industry's
hottest star right now.
As a shot in the dark,
I called his management team.
I didn't expect
his management team to be so interested in this.
If Jin Xi comes,
for the 20 shows of 'A Chinese Ghost Story',
I could sell out 21 shows,
and won't even have to give the theater manager a kickback.
Wait a minute.
Does he have any experience performing in musicals?
Ning Jin.
Don't smile at me like that.
Every time you smile at me like that,
nothing good ever happens.
Ning Jin.
Well,
she is
the most popular singer nowadays.
With that singing skill and popularity,
could I arrange things blindly?
Go sit over there.
Lao Wu.
A singer and a musical actor are two different things.
If he doesn't have stage experience,
it's impossible for me to train him
to be the male lead of a musical
in just two months.
I understand.
When we signed the contract,
I promised you
that I would never interfere with the creative process.
But this great opportunity
fell from the sky,
we have to catch it.
Tonight,
his manager wants to treat me to a late-night snack.
The singer is coming too.
Don't refuse just yet.
Let's give it a try.
Jin.
Give me a chance.
Okay?
Jinxi! Jinxi!
Never leave you!
Love you forever!
Jinxi,
where are you?
Let us see you!
Let me tell you,
our Jinxi
is fully booked
for a long time.
But he just loves musicals,
has loved them since childhood,
and insisted I get him one.
So here we are,
he's going to be in a musical.
Nothing compares to passion.
When I told
our director about this,
he couldn't stop smiling.
The director also told me
that rehearsing a play is like fighting a war,
and actors are the weapons.
If you have a handy weapon,
there's no battle you can't win.
If the director is Guan Yu,
your Jinxi is Diaochan—
no,
the Green Dragon Crescent Blade.
Isn't this a match made in heaven?
I brought the stamp to sign with you.
It's a deal.
What deal?
I am the only one
who has the final say on the lead actor I wrote.
I haven't even met
this actor yet.
What are you deciding here?
But this is Jinxi.
Sorry,
I don't really listen to pop music.
And I don't want to decide the lead actor
just because of a dinner.
Excuse me.
This is a live performance,
a stage.
I must see him in person.
Ning Jin
is the backbone of our troupe.
I highly respect her creative work.
Boss Wu,
that's not what we agreed on before.
I don't care what Lao Wu told you.
But
to play Ning Caichen,
he must attend the audition.
I'm done eating.
I'll take my leave.
Director.
I'll take my leave as well.
This...
Director, can we start?
Director.
Please start your performance.
Start.
Four is four, ten is ten,
fourteen is fourteen,
forty is forty.
Stop.
We don't have a tongue twister segment.
I learned this for a web drama
from a teacher I hired before.
He said I'm really good at tongue twisters.
I also prepared a kissing scene.
No, an action scene.
No need for the action scene.
Just start your song selection.
What song are you going to sing?
Give me the backing track.
It's fine. No need.
I brought my own backing track.
Brother Xi.
Ready.
Who is this?
You don't even know Jin Xi?
No.
You must watch music variety shows even if you don't listen to music.
He's super popular now.
Isn't this Huizi?
Man, thanks for coming to support.
Hey, don't mention it.
Call me anytime if you need anything. I'll be there.
Good luck!
Okay.
Goodbye, Hui.
Take a five-minute break.
Let's take a five-minute break.
We'll continue later.
Director.
You're actually a director.
What are you talking about?
Well, I
went to Zeri Bar the next day
to look for you.
You are Jin Xi, right?
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
You must have the wrong person.
How could I have the wrong person?
I have such a good memory.
And how could I forget
the person I kissed?
Shh.
Don't say that word again.
You two are having a good chat.
Already chatting away.
Jinxi, I'm your fan.
Let's officially meet.
I'm the director of Xiyin Troupe,
Wu Qiming.
Hello, Director.
And this is our...
Xiyin Troupe's exclusive director,
Ning Jin.
You sang really well just now.
Right,
Xiaoning?
It was pretty good.
But unfortunately,
we don't have rap-oriented tracks.
A star is indeed a star.
Look at that stage presence.
So solid and sharp.
Hello, Director.
I'm Jin Xi's manager, Sister Hu.
We've met before.
What do you think?
Are you satisfied with Jin Xi's performance just now?
Not bad.
But I still need to think about it.
Director, actually I still have a lot
to discuss with you about this role.
That's good.
But I still have
more interviewees later.
Today, I already have
a basic impression of you.
If there's a possibility for us
to work together in the future,
I will definitely notify you.
I'll be going now.
Director, would you like to hear
Jinxi's slow songs?
I already know enough.
Director, you will too.
I can play and sing a little.
No need.
Sister Hu, right?
If there is any news,
I will inform you immediately.
Okay.
Old Wu.
Then can we...
Jin Xi.
Okay.
I am here for an interview today.
We can talk later.
But,
let's talk another day.
Okay, director.
Okay.
Bye, director.
That rapper today,
what was his deal?
Singing hip-hop,
isn't that too much?
Does he know what the style
of the musical he is auditioning for is?
Old Wu forced him on us.
He said it helps the box office.
That's why I say
I hate it most
when amateurs interfere with professionals.
In Wu Qiming's head,
besides money,
is there anything else?
He has his difficulties.
Director.
You're not really considering him, are you?
Even a blind person can see that
Heying is
the perfect choice for Ning Caichen.
Of course I know that.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
I'll be leaving then.
Jinxi Middle School.
No.
No!
Qianqian, no.
How was the audition today, bro?
So talented.
Director,
over here.
What would you like to drink?
I'll have this.
Thank you.
Give it to me.
First, a greeting gift.
Here.
What is this?
Look.
The director is both beautiful
and talented.
How is it?
Singing and dancing,
do I look like a musical actor?
Let me tell you.
How do I turn this off?
Just press its bottom.
Director,
since the tickets for the last musical
were all complimentary,
I really want to thank you
for letting me see such a wonderful show.
Consider this
a return gift.
I didn't give them to you.
Lao Wu did.
But I was watching your play.
I'm sorry.
I drank too much that day
and did something out of line to you.
I'm meeting you here today
just to apologize to you.
If I didn't want to smooch you,
I could have dodged it.
No one really uses
the word 'smooch' anymore.
I mean,
in that kind of atmosphere,
I actually wanted to kiss you.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Jin Xi.
Can we stop
bringing up the kiss?
Can we just forget it ever happened?
I get it.
Since we'll be working together every day,
seeing each other
and thinking about it
might be a bit awkward.
Right? I get it.
That brings me to the second thing
I wanted to tell you.
Did Mr. Wu promise you
that the male lead
is already set for you?
Not really.
But he told me
you all really wanted to work with me.
Whether to let you play Ning Caichen
in this role,
I am still considering it.
Why?
Because...
I understand.
Is it because of my song choice at the audition?
I actually chose rap
because I wanted to show my passion
to everyone.
Actually, I also prepared a slow song.
But now I have a better idea.
Great. Sounds great.
Great.
How is it, Director?
This is my...
This is the theme song of your first
urban musical, "Nintendo".
How did you know that?
After watching the performance last time,
I went back
and listened to all your songs.
Sorry, I thought
you were a male director.
I didn't expect you to be so pretty
and talented.
So,
did I pass the audition?
Not yet.
I still need to think about it.
Did I do something wrong?
Jin Xi,
before you came,
I also did some research on you,
including watching some
of your previous screen works.
Did you watch "The Legend of Huayue"?
Director,
don't read those comments.
Those comments...
Screen acting and musical acting
have different requirements.
Every director's requirements for actors
are also different.
As for those screen works
you've acted in before,
I won't make any comments.
However,
do you lack any
stage performance experience?
Yes.
Nowadays, in the market,
most stage actors
have gone through professional institutions'
strict four-year training,
not to mention musical actors
who are excellent in singing,
dancing, and acting.
I know
you are a top talent as a singer.
But,
in terms of stage performance and physical movement,
you are obviously a blank slate.
So,
like the wooden barrel effect,
my shortcomings
dragged me down.
I know
many screen actors now
want to try stage performance.
But for them,
it's just a gimmick,
a gimmick to prove their abilities.
But this is a profession I love deeply.
If you are just playing around
by joining my musical,
I advise you to think it over carefully.
Do you understand?
This script
is worth investing in.
Indeed.
Don't hesitate.
Is Jinxi here?
Yes. This is an
artistic feast of mutual appreciation.
What's wrong, Ning Jin?
Lao Wu.
For the male lead in 'A Chinese Ghost Story',
I still want to cast Heying.
What about Jinxi?
He is excellent,
but I'm not sure
if he can handle the leading role.
After all, rather than gimmicks,
I care more about the play's quality.
That is the very foundation of my livelihood.
Okay.
I understand.
One little bee,
flying, smack, smack.
Sister Hu,
there's something
I need to tell you.
For this production of A Chinese Ghost Story,
although the audition is open to the public,
after a round of interviews,
it's basically still a gathering of
our familiar faces.
Now,
let me announce
the casting for the main roles.
The role of Lao Lao goes to
Big Cousin.
The role of Yan Chixia goes to
Jiao Ye.
The role of Black Mountain Demon goes to
Qingsong.
The female lead,
the role of Nie Xiaoqian...
Me.
That's right.
It's still our familiar Bai Feixin.
The male lead, the role of Ning Caichen,
is naturally played by our excellent...
Jin Xi.
I'm sorry for not notifying everyone earlier.
Now,
I'd like to officially give you all a little surprise.
Today, I officially announce
that our Xiyin Theater Troupe
will sign singer Jin Xi
to be
the undisputed male lead of "A Chinese Ghost Story",
Ning Caichen.
I believe that with Jin Xi joining us,
our theater troupe and this play
will definitely have a huge impact.
Here,
Director Ning,
and everyone else, please help
Jin Xi.
Let's make this play a success together.
Hello everyone, my name is Jin Xi.
Nice to meet you all.
I really look forward to joining this family.
Thank you.
Great.